### Contact

amangoeliitb@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amangoeliitb (LinkedIn)

www.getcogno.ai (Company)

## Top Skills

Machine Learning
Deep Learning

**Python** 

### Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

### Honors-Awards

Institute Academic Award
Gold Medal and Certificate of Merit
Honoured by the CIO and CTO of
the State Bank of India

# **Aman Goel**

Co-founder and CEO at Cogno AI (AllinCall) | IIT Bombay Mumbai

# Summary

Technology Entrepreneur with the experience of developing Software Products for large enterprises.

Hiring for multiple roles.

Careers: https://hr.allincall.in/hr-manager/careers/

Campuses: https://lnkd.in/f2BPMa2

Please do not message or mail me the resumes for job application.

They would not be seen.

# Experience

AllinCall

Co-founder & CEO

April 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Cogno AI by AllinCall is an Enterprise User Engagement Platform that uses a combination of Artificial & Human Intelligence to help enterprises in assisting customers during the Onboarding journey.

Select Clientele: ICICI Group, Kotak Group, Bajaj, IDFC FIRST Bank, etc.

Website: https://getcogno.ai/

Reverie Row

Co-Founder

June 2016 - April 2017 (11 months)

Mumbai Area, India

- Providing technical and educational content writing services to multiple clients.
- Achieved revenues of over US \$50,000.
- Lead a team of ~20 freelancers.

- Discontinued because I found a much bigger opportunity at AllinCall, my latest venture.

Aman's Blog Co-founder June 2013 - June 2016 (3 years 1 month) Mumbai Area, India

- Created a blog on JEE preparation mentoring thousands of students reaching 3.5 million+ page views.
- Funded my college education with the revenues earned from the blog.

## Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science and
Engineering · (2013 - 2017)